angliaceramics.co.uk 2019-04-02

# Anglia Ceramics - Specialised crown and bridge laboratory, Peterborough

This Privacy Policy informs you of our commitment to privacy and explains the ways that _**Anglia Ceramics**_ collects, uses and discloses your personal and non-personal information when you visit this website. By visiting this site, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

_**Anglia Ceramics**_ reserves the right to modify the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice, and such modifications shall be effective immediately upon posting of the modified Privacy Policy on this website. You agree to review this Privacy Policy periodically to be aware of such modifications and your continued use of the website following the posting of any modified terms shall be deemed your conclusive acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any modifications posted by Anglia Ceramics your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue use of this website. 

**Collecting and Using Information**  
We will not collect personal information about you when you visit our website, unless you choose to directly provide such information when contacting us via email, by completing online forms, or posting to any website online interactive areas such as forums, where such areas exist. We do not disclose any personal information, however obtained through this website, without explicit permission from the person to whom it relates. 

We will use this personal information to process your request and, when applicable, respond to you. By contacting us in this manner, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information for the purpose of responding to your request. 

We do store information collected from visitors for statistical monitoring purposes and to help us respond to comments made about the site. 

**Cookies**   
A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. 

We use third party cookies from StatCounter.com to analyse the use of this website. StatCounter.com generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. StatCounter.com will store this information. View StatCounter.com privacy policy. 

**Protecting Information**  
We strive to protect all personal information we receive online with appropriate safeguards and security measures. However, the Internet is not a secure medium and neither the privacy of your communications, nor that of visitors to this website, can be ensured. Accordingly, by visiting this website, you acknowledge and agree that Anglia Ceramics does not guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and that you do so at your own risk. 

**Providing Access and Maintaining Accuracy**  
We will provide access to the personal information we collect and retain about you and use all reasonable efforts to maintain the accuracy of your personal information. 

This privacy policy does not cover any links to third party sites. 

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or wish information about how to access any of your personal information held at _**Anglia Ceramics**_ website, please email us at [ angliaceramics@aol.com](mailto:angliaceramics@aol.com)
